A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1940-1946 FA758
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1944
  - Bahamas, 1944; 1944/433
    - Bahamas, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1882)
    - Bahamas - Medical Sciences, 1944; 1944/433.A
      - Bahamas, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1882)
  - Barbados, 1944; 1944/435
    Barbados
    - Barbados - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1944; 1944/435.E
      - Barbados, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1882)
    - Barbados - Malaria, 1944; 1944/435.I
      - Barbados, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1882)
  - Jamaica, 1944; 1944/437
    - Jamaica, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1883)
    - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, 1944; 1944/437.A
      - Jamaica, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1883)
    - Jamaica - Nursing, 1944; 1944/437.C
      - Jamaica, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1883)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1944; 1944/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1883)
  - Dominica, 1944; 1944/443
    Dominica
    - Dominica, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1883)
  - Trinidad, 1944; 1944/451
    - Trinidad, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1883)
  - Windward Islands, 1944; 1944/455
    - Windward Islands, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1883)
    - Windward Islands - Medical Sciences, 1944; 1944/455.A
      - Windward Islands, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1883)
  - St. Vincent, 1944; 1944/459
    Saint Vincent and the Grenadines
    - St. Vincent, 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1883)
  - India, 1944; 1944/464
    - India - (A-B), 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1884)
    - India - (Cholera), 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1885)
    - India - (D-I), 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1886)
    - India - (I-Z), 1944 (Box 275, Folder 1887)
    - BAL-1 Balfour, Marshall C. "Current Problems of India and China in Relations to Tropical Medicine", 1944 (Box 562, Folder 3827)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1944; 1944/464.A
      - India, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
    - India - Nursing, 1944; 1944/464.C
      - India, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1944; 1944/464.E
      - India, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
    - India - Respiratory Diseases, 1944; 1944/464.M
      - India, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
    - India - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/464.R
      - India, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1944; 1944/464.S
      - India, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
  - Iraq, 1944; 1944/470
    - Iraq, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
    - Iraq - Malaria, 1944; 1944/470.I
      - Iraq, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
  - Africa, 1944; 1944/475
    - Africa, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1944; 1944/475.S
      - Africa, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
  - Mauritius, 1944; 1944/478
    Mauritius
    - Mauritius, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
    - Mauritius - Malaria, 1944; 1944/478.I
      - Mauritius, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1888)
  - North Africa Region, 1944; 1944/485
    - North Africa, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1889)
    - North Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1944; 1944/485.E
      - North Africa, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1889)
    - North Africa Region - Yellow Fever, 1944; 1944/485.O
      - North Africa, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1889)
    - North Africa Region - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/485.R
      - North Africa, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1889)
  - South Africa Region, 1944; 1944/487
    - South Africa, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1889)
    - South Africa Region - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/487.R
      - South Africa, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1889)
  - France, 1944; 1944/500
    - France, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1890)
    - France - Medical Sciences, 1944; 1944/500.A
      - France, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1890)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1944; 1944/500.E
      - France, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1890)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/500.R
      - France, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1890)
    - France- Social Sciences, 1944; 1944/500.S
      - France, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1890)
  - Asia, 1944; 1944/600
    - Asia, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1891)
    - Asia - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/600.R
      - Asia, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1891)
  - China, 1944; 1944/601
    - China, 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1891)
    - China - (General), 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1892)
    - China - (A-G), 1944 (Box 276, Folder 1893)
    - China - (H-P), 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1894)
    - China - (Q-Z), 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1895)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1944; 1944/601.A
      - China, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1896)
    - China - Nursing, 1944; 1944/601.C
      - China, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1896)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1944; 1944/601.E
      - China, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1896)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/601.R
      - China, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1896)
    - China - Social Sciences, 1944; 1944/601.S
      - China, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1896)
  - Japan, 1944; 1944/609
    - Japan - Social Sciences, 1944; 1944/609.S
      - Japan, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1897)
  - Holland (Netherlands), 1944; 1944/650
    - Netherlands, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1897)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1944; 1944/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1897)
  - Indonesia, 1944; 1944/652
    - Indonesia - Medical Sciences, 1944; 1944/652.A
      - Indonesia, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1897)
  - Europe, 1944; 1944/700
    - Europe, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1897)
  - Ethiopia, 1944; 1944/701
    Ethiopia
    - Ethiopia, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1898)
  - Belgium, 1944; 1944/707
    - Belgium, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1898)
    - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/707.R
      - Belgium, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1898)
  - Yugoslavia, 1944; 1944/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1898)
  - Denmark, 1944; 1944/713
    - Denmark, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1898)
    - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/713.R
      - Denmark, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1898)
  - Germany, 1944; 1944/717
    - Germany, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1899)
  - Greenland, 1944; 1944/718
    - Greenland - Tuberculosis, 1944; 1944/718.T
      - Greenland, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1899)
  - Hungary, 1944; 1944/750
    - Hungary, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1899)
  - Italy, 1944; 1944/751
    - Italy, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1899)
    - Italy - Nursing, 1944; 1944/751.C
      - Italy, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1899)
  - Norway, 1944; 1944/767
    - Norway, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1899)
    - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/767.R
      - Norway, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1899)
  - Iran, 1944; 1944/771
    - Iran, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1900)
  - Portugal, 1944; 1944/773
    - Portugal, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1900)
  - Ukrainia, 1944; 1944/784
    Ukraine
    - Ukrainia, 1944 (Box 277, Folder 1900)
  - U.S.S.R., 1944; 1944/785
    - U. S. S. R., 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1901)
    - U.S.S.R. - Medical Sciences, 1944; 1944/785.A
      - U. S. S. R., 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1901)
    - U.S.S.R. - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1944; 1944/785.D
      - U. S. S. R., 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1901)
    - U.S.S.R. - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/785.R
      - U. S. S. R., 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1901)
    - U.S.S.R. - Social Sciences, 1944; 1944/785.S
      - U. S. S. R., 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1901)
  - Finland, 1944; 1944/787
    - Finland, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
  - Poland, 1944; 1944/789
    - Poland, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1944; 1944/789.E
      - Poland, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
  - Sweden, 1944; 1944/800
    - Sweden, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1944; 1944/800.E
      - Sweden, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
    - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/800.R
      - Sweden, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
  - Switzerland, 1944; 1944/803
    - Switzerland, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
    - Switzerland - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/803.R
      - Switzerland, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
    - Switzerland - Social Sciences, 1944; 1944/803.S
      - Switzerland, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
  - Near East Region, 1944; 1944/804
    - Near East Region - Humanities and Arts, 1944; 1944/804.R
      - Near East, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
  - Turkey, 1944; 1944/805
    - Turkey, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
  - Lebanon, 1944; 1944/833
    - Lebanon, 1944 (Box 278, Folder 1902)
- General Correspondence, 1945
  - International, 1945; 1945/100
    - (A), 1945 (Box 278, Folder 1903)
    - Balfour, M. C. - 1, 1945 (Box 278, Folder 1904)
    - Balfour, M. C. - 2, 1945 (Box 278, Folder 1905)
    - Balfour, M. C. - 3, 1945 (Box 278, Folder 1906)
    - Balfour, M. C. - 4, 1945 (Box 279, Folder 1907)
    - Balfour, M. C. - 5, 1945 (Box 279, Folder 1908)
    - (Ba-Be), 1945 (Box 279, Folder 1909)
    - Bevier, George, 1945 (Box 279, Folder 1910)
    - Bugher, John C., 1945 (Box 279, Folder 1911)
    - Carr, Henry P. - 1, 1945 (Box 280, Folder 1912)
    - Carr, Henry P. - 2, 1945 (Box 280, Folder 1913)
    - Carr, Henry P. - 3, 1945 (Box 280, Folder 1914)
    - (Ca), 1945 (Box 280, Folder 1915)
    - (Co-Di), 1945 (Box 280, Folder 1916)
    - Dyer, Brian R. - 1, 1945 (Box 280, Folder 1917)
    - Dyer, Brian R. - 2, 1945 (Box 281, Folder 1918)
    - Elmendorf, John E., 1945 (Box 281, Folder 1919)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B. - 1, 1945 (Box 281, Folder 1920)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B. - 2, 1945 (Box 281, Folder 1921)
    - (Fo-Go), 1945 (Box 281, Folder 1922)
    - Grant, John B. - 1, 1945 (Box 281, Folder 1923)
    - Grant, John B. - 2, 1945 (Box 282, Folder 1924)
    - Grant, John B. - 3, 1945 (Box 282, Folder 1925)
    - Hackett, Lewis W. - 1, 1945 (Box 282, Folder 1926)
    - Hackett, Lewis W. - 2, 1945 (Box 282, Folder 1927)
    - Hahn, Richard G., 1945 (Box 282, Folder 1928)
    - Hayes, Guy S., 1945 (Box 282, Folder 1929)
    - Hill, Rolla B., 1945 (Box 283, Folder 1930)
    - Hirst, Esther M., 1945 (Box 283, Folder 1931)
    - (Hi-Hu), 1945 (Box 283, Folder 1932)
    - Janney, John H. - 1, 1945 (Box 283, Folder 1933)
    - Janney, John H. - 2, 1945 (Box 283, Folder 1934)
    - Johnson, Harold N., 1945 (Box 283, Folder 1934)
    - Kendrick, J. F., 1945 (Box 283, Folder 1935)
    - Kerr, J. Austin - 1, 1945 (Box 283, Folder 1935)
    - Kerr, J. Austin - 2, 1945 (Box 284, Folder 1936)
    - Kitchen, S. F., 1945 (Box 284, Folder 1936)
    - Leach, Charles N. - 1, 1945 (Box 284, Folder 1937)
    - Leach, Charles N. - 2, 1945 (Box 284, Folder 1938)
    - Leach, Charles N. - 3, 1945 (Box 284, Folder 1939)
    - Lennette, Edwin H., 1945 (Box 284, Folder 1940)
    - McIntosh, W. A. - 1, 1945 (Box 284, Folder 1941)
    - McIntosh, W. A. - 2, 1945 (Box 284, Folder 1942)
    - Magoon, E. H. - Mailing Lists, 1945 (Box 285, Folder 1943)
    - Marshall, John, 1945 (Box 285, Folder 1944)
    - Milam, D. Frank, 1945 (Box 285, Folder 1945)
    - Miller, H. M., 1945 (Box 285, Folder 1946)
    - Muench, Hugo, 1945 (Box 285, Folder 1947)
    - Nutrition - O'Brien, Daniel P., 1945 (Box 285, Folder 1948)
    - Paul, J. H., 1945 (Box 285, Folder 1949)
    - Payne, G. C. - 1, 1945 (Box 285, Folder 1949)
    - Payne, G. C. - 2, 1945 (Box 286, Folder 1950)
    - Peterson, O. L., 1945 (Box 286, Folder 1951)
    - Psychiatry - 1, 1945 (Box 286, Folder 1952)
    - Psychiatry - 2, 1945 (Box 286, Folder 1953)
    - (Pu-Ru), 1945 (Box 286, Folder 1954)
    - Shannon, Raymond C., 1945 (Box 286, Folder 1955)
    - Smith, H. H., 1945 (Box 286, Folder 1955)
    - Smithburn, Kenneth C., 1945 (Box 286, Folder 1956)
    - Soper, Fred L., 1945 (Box 287, Folder 1957)
    - Strode, George K. - 1, 1945 (Box 287, Folder 1958)
    - Strode, George K. - 2, 1945 (Box 287, Folder 1959)
    - Taylor, Richard M., 1945 (Box 287, Folder 1960)
    - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth - 1, 1945 (Box 287, Folder 1961)
    - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth - 2, 1945 (Box 287, Folder 1962)
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization - United Nations Food and Agriculture Organization - Warren, A. J., 1945 (Box 287, Folder 1963)
    - Watson, Robert B., 1945 (Box 288, Folder 1964)
    - Weir, John M., 1945 (Box 288, Folder 1964)
    - Wells, C. W., 1945 (Box 288, Folder 1964)
    - Wells, C. W., 1945 (Box 288, Folder 1965)
    - (Wh-Wo), 1945 (Box 288, Folder 1966)
    - Miscellaneous - (A-B), 1945 (Box 288, Folder 1967)
    - Miscellaneous - (C-K), 1945 (Box 288, Folder 1968)
    - Miscellaneous - (L-Ra), 1945 (Box 288, Folder 1969)
    - Miscellaneous - (Ri), 1945 (Box 289, Folder 1970)
    - International - Nursing, 1945; 1945/100.C
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1945 (Box 289, Folder 1971)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1945; 1945/100.O
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1945 (Box 289, Folder 1971)
    - International - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/100.S
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1945 (Box 289, Folder 1972)
    - International - Tuberculosis, 1945; 1945/100.T
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1945 (Box 289, Folder 1972)
  - United States, 1945; 1945/200
    - United States - (A-Amer B), 1945 (Box 289, Folder 1973)
    - United States - (Amer-C-R), 1945 (Box 289, Folder 1974)
    - United States - (Amer R-Arm), 1945 (Box 289, Folder 1975)
    - United States - (Ar-Ba), 1945 (Box 290, Folder 1976)
    - United States - (Be-Bz), 1945 (Box 290, Folder 1977)
    - United States - (C-Cl), 1945 (Box 290, Folder 1978)
    - United States - (Cl-Co), 1945 (Box 290, Folder 1979)
    - United States - (Co-Cz), 1945 (Box 290, Folder 1980)
    - United States - (D-Do), 1945 (Box 290, Folder 1981)
    - United States - (Du-Fi), 1945 (Box 291, Folder 1982)
    - United States - (Fi-Fz), 1945 (Box 291, Folder 1983)
    - United States - (G), 1945 (Box 291, Folder 1984)
    - United States - (H-Har), 1945 (Box 291, Folder 1985)
    - United States - Harvard - (A-H), 1945 (Box 291, Folder 1986)
    - United States - Harvard - (I-Z), 1945 (Box 291, Folder 1987)
    - United States - (Has-Hz), 1945 (Box 291, Folder 1988)
    - United States - (I), 1945 (Box 292, Folder 1989)
    - United States - (J), 1945 (Box 292, Folder 1990)
    - United States - (L), 1945 (Box 292, Folder 1991)
    - United States - (M-Me), 1945 (Box 292, Folder 1992)
    - United States - (Me-Na), 1945 (Box 292, Folder 1993)
    - United States - (Ne-Oz), 1945 (Box 292, Folder 1994)
    - United States - (P), 1945 (Box 293, Folder 1995)
    - United States - Princeton, 1945 (Box 293, Folder 1996)
    - United States - (Q-Refugee Scholars), 1945 (Box 293, Folder 1997)
    - United States - (R), 1945 (Box 293, Folder 1998)
    - United States - (Sa-Sz), 1945 (Box 293, Folder 1999)
    - United States - (Sa-Sz), 1945 (Box 293, Folder 2000)
    - United States - (T-United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration), 1945 (Box 294, Folder 2001)
    - United States - (T-United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration), 1945 (Box 294, Folder 2002)
    - United States - (U.S. A-R), 1945 (Box 294, Folder 2003)
    - United States - (U.S. A-R), 1945 (Box 294, Folder 2004)
    - United States - Scientific Research Fund - 1-3, 1945 (Box 294, Folder 2005)
    - United States - Scientific Research Fund - 1-3, 1945 (Box 294, Folder 2006)
    - United States - Scientific Research Fund - 1-3, 1945 (Box 294, Folder 2007)
    - United States - Scientific Research Fund - 4, 1945 (Box 295, Folder 2008)
    - United States - (United States Se-Z), 1945 (Box 295, Folder 2009)
    - United States - (Un-Vz), 1945 (Box 295, Folder 2010)
    - United States - (W-Z), 1945 (Box 295, Folder 2011)
    - United States - (W-Z), 1945 (Box 295, Folder 2012)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/200.A
      - United States - (A-M), 1945 (Box 295, Folder 2013)
      - United States - (M-Z), 1945 (Box 296, Folder 2014)
      - United States - (M-Z), 1945 (Box 296, Folder 2015)
    - United States - Nursing, 1945; 1945/200.C
      - United States, 1945 (Box 296, Folder 2016)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/200.D
      - United States, 1945 (Box 296, Folder 2016)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/200.E
      - United States, 1945 (Box 296, Folder 2017)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (A-Be), 1945 (Box 296, Folder 2018)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (Bi-Cr), 1945 (Box 296, Folder 2019)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (Cr-D), 1945 (Box 297, Folder 2020)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (Ce-F), 1945 (Box 297, Folder 2021)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (G-Mac), 1945 (Box 297, Folder 2022)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (G-Mac), 1945 (Box 297, Folder 2023)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (G-Mac), 1945 (Box 297, Folder 2024)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (Mad-Z), 1945 (Box 298, Folder 2025)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (Mad-Z), 1945 (Box 298, Folder 2026)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (Mad-Z), 1945 (Box 298, Folder 2027)
      - United States - Postwar Fellowships - (Mad-Z), 1945 (Box 298, Folder 2028)
    - United States - Declinations, 1945; 1945/200.F
      - United States, 1945 (Box 298, Folder 2029)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/200.R
      - United States, 1945 (Box 298, Folder 2029)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/200.S
      - United States - (A-S), 1945 (Box 298, Folder 2030)
      - United States - Social Science Research Council - (L-Z), 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2031)
  - Alabama, 1945; 1945/201
    - Alabama, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2032)
  - California, 1945; 1945/205
    - California, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2032)
    - California - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/205.A
      - California, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2033)
    - California - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/205.R
      - California, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2033)
    - California - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/205.S
      - California, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2033)
  - Colorado, 1945; 1945/207
    - Colorado, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2033)
  - Florida, 1945; 1945/211
    - Florida, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2033)
  - Georgia, 1945; 1945/212
    - Georgia, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2033)
  - Hawaii, 1945; 1945/214
    - Hawaii, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2033)
  - Illinois, 1945; 1945/216
    - Illinois, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2034)
    - Illinois - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/216.S
      - Illinois, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2034)
  - Indiana, 1945; 1945/217
    Indiana
    - Indiana, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2035)
  - Kentucky, 1945; 1945/220
    - Kentucky, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2035)
  - Maine, 1945; 1945/222
    - Maine, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2035)
  - Massachusetts, 1945; 1945/224
    - Massachusetts, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2035)
    - Massachusetts - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/224.A
      - Massachusetts, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2035)
  - Mississippi, 1945; 1945/227
    - Mississippi, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2035)
  - New Jersey, 1945; 1945/233
    - New Jersey, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2036)
  - New York, 1945; 1945/235
    - New York, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2036)
  - North Carolina, 1945; 1945/236
    - North Carolina, 1945 (Box 299, Folder 2036)
  - Ohio, 1945; 1945/238
    - Ohio, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2037)
    - Ohio - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/238.R
      - Ohio, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2037)
  - Pennsylvania, 1945; 1945/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2037)
    - Pennsylvania - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/241.R
      - Pennsylvania, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2037)
  - Philippines, 1945; 1945/242
    - Philippines, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2037)
    - Philippines - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/242.A
      - Philippines, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2037)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/242.E
      - Philippines, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2037)
  - Puerto Rico, 1945; 1945/243
    Puerto Rico
    - Puerto Rico, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2038)
  - Rhode Island, 1945; 1945/244
    - Rhode Island, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2038)
  - Tennessee, 1945; 1945/248
    - Tennessee, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2038)
  - Texas, 1945; 1945/249
    - Texas, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2039)
  - Washington, 1945; 1945/253
    - Washington, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2039)
  - Wisconsin, 1945; 1945/255
    - Wisconsin, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2039)
  - Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands, 1945; 1945/258
    Pacific Islands
    - Pacific Islands Trust, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2039)
  - South America, 1945; 1945/300
    - South America - Administration, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2040)
    - South America - Administration, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2041)
    - South America, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2042)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/300.A
      - South America, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2042)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/300.D
      - South America, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2042)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/300.E
      - South America, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2042)
    - South America - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/300.R
      - South America, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2042)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/300.S
      - South America, 1945 (Box 300, Folder 2042)
  - Argentina, 1945; 1945/301
    - Argentina - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2043)
    - Argentina - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2044)
    - Argentina - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/301.A
      - Argentina, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2045)
    - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/301.D
      - Argentina, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2045)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/301.E
      - Argentina, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2045)
  - Bolivia, 1945; 1945/303
    - Bolivia, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2045)
    - Bolivia - Nursing, 1945; 1945/303.C
      - Bolivia, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2045)
  - Brazil, 1945; 1945/305
    - Brazil, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2046)
    - Brazil - Nursing, 1945; 1945/305.C
      - Brazil, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2047)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/305.E
      - Brazil, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2047)
    - Brazil - Malaria, 1945; 1945/305.I
      - Brazil, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2047)
    - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1945; 1945/305.O
      - Brazil, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2047)
    - Brazil - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/305.R
      - Brazil, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2047)
  - Chile, 1945; 1945/309
    - Chile, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2048)
    - Chile - Nursing, 1945; 1945/309.C
      - Chile, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2048)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/309.E
      - Chile, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2048)
  - Colombia, 1945; 1945/311
    - Colombia - Administration, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2048)
    - Colombia, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2049)
    - Colombia, 1945 (Box 301, Folder 2049)
  - Costa Rica, 1945; 02.1945/313
    - Costa Rica, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2050)
  - Cuba, 1945; 02.1945/315
    - Cuba, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2050)
  - Ecuador, 1945; 1945/317
    - Ecuador, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2051)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/317.E
      - Ecuador, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2051)
    - Ecuador - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/317.R
      - Guatemala, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2051)
  - Honduras, 1945; 1945/321
    - Honduras, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2051)
  - Mexico, 1945; 1945/323
    - Mexico - Administration, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2052)
    - Mexico, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2053)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/323.A
      - Mexico, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2053)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/323.E
      - Mexico, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2053)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/323.R
      - Mexico, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2053)
  - Nicaragua, 1945; 1945/325
    - Nicaragua, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2054)
    - Nicaragua - Nursing, 1945; 1945/325.C